Correspondence, 1920-2007
Smithsonian Institution Archives
Correspondence
1920-2007
Smithsonian Institution Archives, Washington, D.C., osiaref@si.edu
National Museum of Natural History, Division of Mollusks
SI Records
13 cu. ft. (13 record storage boxes)
Accession 08-172
Descriptive Entry
This accession consists of incoming and outgoing divisional correspondence concerning specimen identification, data exchanges, manuscripts, grant proposals, exhibits, and other activities of the Division of Mollusks.
Index Terms
This collection is indexed under the following access terms. These are links to collections with related topics, persons or places.
Subject
Invertebrates; Marine invertebrates; Mollusks.
Physical Characteristics of Materials in the Collection
Manuscripts
- Box 1
  - A ,1991 (Box 1 of 13)
  - A, 2003 (Box 1 of 13)
  - A, 2002 (Box 1 of 13)
  - A, 2001 (Box 1 of 13)
  - A, 1998 (Box 1 of 13)
  - A, 1996 (Box 1 of 13)
  - A, 1995 (Box 1 of 13)
  - A, 1994 (Box 1 of 13)
  - A, 1993 (Box 1 of 13)
  - A, 1989 (Box 1 of 13)
  - A, 1992 (Box 1 of 13)
  - Aa-Ab, 1987-1991 (Box 1 of 13)
  - Ac-Ag, 1982-1985 (Box 1 of 13)
  - Ah-Ald, 1975-1988 (Box 1 of 13)
  - Ale-Alk, 1977-1990 (Box 1 of 13)
  - All-Allen, B, 1976-1978 (Box 1 of 13)
  - Allen, C. - Allen, 1975-1982 (Box 1 of 13)
  - All-Als, 1978-1982 (Box 1 of 13)
  - Alt-Alz, 1980-1988 (Box 1 of 13)
  - Am, 1976-1983 (Box 1 of 13)
  - An-Anderson, 1976-1978 (Box 1 of 13)
  - Ande-Andrews, 1987-1989 (Box 1 of 13)
  - Andr-Ang, 1977-1979 (Box 1 of 13)
  - Ank-Anz, 1976-1978 (Box 1 of 13)
  - Ao-Arg, 1978-1989 (Box 1 of 13)
  - Ari-Arm, 1981-1990 (Box 1 of 13)
  - Arn-As, 1977-1988 (Box 1 of 13)
  - As-Ask, 1988-1990 (Box 1 of 13)
  - Asl-At, 1976-1900 (Box 1 of 13)
  - Au-Az, 1974-1986 (Box 1 of 13)
  - Abbott, R. T. (2 folders) (Box 1 of 13)
  - Adam, William (Box 1 of 13)
  - Alexander, Robert (Box 1 of 13)
  - Allen, J. A. (Box 1 of 13)
  - Altena, C. O. van R. (Box 1 of 13)
  - Apte, D. (Box 1 of 13)
  - B, 2004 (Box 1 of 13)
  - B, 2003 (Box 1 of 13)
  - B, 2002 (Box 1 of 13)
  - B, 2001 (Box 1 of 13)
  - B, 2000 (Box 1 of 13)
  - B, 1999 (Box 1 of 13)
  - B, 1998 (Box 1 of 13)
  - B, 1997 (Box 1 of 13)
  - B, 1994 (Box 1 of 13)
  - B, 1993 (Box 1 of 13)
  - B, 1995 (Box 1 of 13)
  - B, 1996 (Box 1 of 13)
  - B, 1992 (Box 1 of 13)
  - B, 1991 (Box 1 of 13)
  - B, 1990 (Box 1 of 13)
  - B, 1989 (Box 1 of 13)
  - Ba-Bak, 1976-1989 (Box 1 of 13)
  - Baker, 1978-1989 (Box 1 of 13)
  - Bal-Ball, 1975-1988 (Box 1 of 13)
  - Bam-Baq, 1975-1989 (Box 1 of 13)
  - Barb, 1978-1991 (Box 1 of 13)
  - Barc-Barl, 1975-1990 (Box 1 of 13)
  - Barm-Barz, 1969-1982 (Box 1 of 13)
  - Bas, 1976-1979 (Box 1 of 13)
  - Bat-Bauf, 1977-1983 (Box 1 of 13)
  - Baug-Baz, 1978-1989 (Box 1 of 13)
  - Bea-Beb, 1975-1976 (Box 1 of 13)
  - Bec-Bed, 1978-1982 (Box 1 of 13)
  - Bee, 1976-1986 (Box 1 of 13)
  - Bef-Bel, 1981-1988 (Box 1 of 13)
  - Bell-Ben, 1977-1981 (Box 1 of 13)
  - Benn-Benz, 1977-1989 (Box 1 of 13)
  - Ber, 1975-1980 (Box 1 of 13)
  - Bes-Bez, 1975-1986 (Box 1 of 13)
  - Bh-Bij, 1981-1983 (Box 1 of 13)
- Box 2
  - Bik-Bin, 1984-1989 (Box 2 of 13)
  - Bio-Biz, 1982-1987 (Box 2 of 13)
  - Bla, 1945-1975 (Box 2 of 13)
  - Baker, 1975 (Box 2 of 13)
  - Bayer, F. M. 1979 (Box 2 of 13)
  - Berry, S. Stillman, 1975-1980 (Box 2 of 13)
  - Blea-Bli, 1977-1993 (Box 2 of 13)
  - Blo-Blow, 1978-1988 (Box 2 of 13)
  - Blume, 1981 (Box 2 of 13)
  - Boa-Boe, 1977-1985 (Box 2 of 13)
  - Bof-Bol, 1981-1986 (Box 2 of 13)
  - Bon, 1984-1988 (Box 2 of 13)
  - Boo, 1979-1988 (Box 2 of 13)
  - Bor-Born, 1975-1976 (Box 2 of 13)
  - Bos, 1977-1988 (Box 2 of 13)
  - Boss, K., 1984-1990 (Box 2 of 13)
  - Bot-Bou, 1979-1995 (Box 2 of 13)
  - Bow-Boz, 1975-1983 (Box 2 of 13)
  - Bra-Bram, 1983-1985 (Box 2 of 13)
  - Bran-Braz, 1981-1988 (Box 2 of 13)
  - Bre, 1975-1988 (Box 2 of 13)
  - Bri, 1975-1986 (Box 2 of 13)
  - Bro, 1980-1981 (Box 2 of 13)
  - Broo, 1985-1987 (Box 2 of 13)
  - Brown, 1979-1988 (Box 2 of 13)
  - Brop-Bruz, 1986-1988 (Box 2 of 13)
  - Bru, 1977 (Box 2 of 13)
  - Bry, 1975-1987 (Box 2 of 13)
  - Bul-Bun, 1979-1985 (Box 2 of 13)
  - Bul-Bun, 1975-1985 (Box 2 of 13)
  - Buo-Bur, 1976-1988 (Box 2 of 13)
  - Burn-Burt, 1979-1983 (Box 2 of 13)
  - Bus-But, 1976-1986 (Box 2 of 13)
  - Biese, Walter (Box 2 of 13)
  - Binder, F. (Box 2 of 13)
  - Boss, Kenneth J. (Box 2 of 13)
  - Boswell, Helen (Box 2 of 13)
  - Bratcher, Twila (Box 2 of 13)
  - Britton, J. C. (Box 2 of 13)
  - Building Management (Box 2 of 13)
  - Bullis, Harvey R., JR. (Box 2 of 13)
  - Burch, B. L. (Box 2 of 13)
  - Burch, Tom (Box 2 of 13)
  - Burch, John B (Box 2 of 13)
  - Burch, John Q. (Box 2 of 13)
  - Burgess, Dr. C. (Box 2 of 13)
  - Keel (Box 2 of 13)
  - C, 2002 (Box 2 of 13)
  - C, 2001 (Box 2 of 13)
  - C, 1999 (Box 2 of 13)
  - C, 1998 (Box 2 of 13)
  - C, 1997 (Box 2 of 13)
  - C, 1996 (Box 2 of 13)
  - C, 1994 (Box 2 of 13)
  - C, 1995 (Box 2 of 13)
  - C, 1996 (Box 2 of 13)
  - C, 1993 (Box 2 of 13)
  - C, 1991 (Box 2 of 13)
  - C, 1992 (Box 2 of 13)
  - C, 1989 (Box 2 of 13)
  - C, 1990 (Box 2 of 13)
  - Codoceo (Box 2 of 13)
  - Cal, 1975-1987 (Box 2 of 13)
  - Cal-Cak, 1975-1980 (Box 2 of 13)
  - Cam-Camo, 1980-1995 (Box 2 of 13)
  - Camp (Box 2 of 13)
  - Can-Caq, 1978-1995 (Box 2 of 13)
  - Cara-Cark, 1977-1986 (Box 2 of 13)
  - Carl-Carq, 1977-1987 (Box 2 of 13)
  - Cart-Carz, 1976-1981 (Box 2 of 13)
  - Carr-Cars, 1983-1985 (Box 2 of 13)
  - Cas, 1980-1986 (Box 2 of 13)
  - Cat, 1976-1985 (Box 2 of 13)
  - Ce-Chal, 1986-1988 (Box 2 of 13)
  - Cham 1987 (Box 2 of 13)
  - Chan, 1975-1988 (Box 2 of 13)
  - Chap 1977-1985 (Box 2 of 13)
  - Char-Chas 1977 (Box 2 of 13)
  - Chat-Chaz, 1976-1982 (Box 2 of 13)
  - Che, 1977-1984 (Box 2 of 13)
  - Chi-Cho, 1979-1984 (Box 2 of 13)
  - Chr-Chu, 1981-1986 (Box 2 of 13)
- Box 3
  - Cernohorsky, Walter O. (Box 3 of 13)
  - Cernohorsky, W. (Box 3 of 13)
  - Chace, E. P. (Box 3 of 13)
  - CIAC (Box 3 of 13)
  - Clarke, Arthur H. (Box 3 of 13)
  - Clench, W. J. (Box 3 of 13)
  - Clench, William J. 1970 (Box 3 of 13)
  - Clench, William J. 1920-1930 (Box 3 of 13)
  - Clark (Box 3 of 13)
  - Clarke (Box 3 of 13)
  - Cla-Clap, 1982-1988 (Box 3 of 13)
  - Cle, 1983-1987 (Box 3 of 13)
  - Cli-Clo, 1976-1988 (Box 3 of 13)
  - Coa-Cod, 1986-1988 (Box 3 of 13)
  - Coe-Cok, 1976-1985 (Box 3 of 13)
  - Col, 1975-1985 (Box 3 of 13)
  - Com-Conk, 1975-1985 (Box 3 of 13)
  - Cole (Box 3 of 13)
  - Conn-Cons, 1976-1986 (Box 3 of 13)
  - Coo-Cook, 1975-1988 (Box 3 of 13)
  - Cool-Coop, 1977-1988 (Box 3 of 13)
  - Cop-Cory, 1978-1986 (Box 3 of 13)
  - Cos-Cot, 1976-1984 (Box 3 of 13)
  - Cou-Cow, 1976-1986 (Box 3 of 13)
  - Cox-Coz, 1985-1986 (Box 3 of 13)
  - Cra-Cram, 1981-1986 (Box 3 of 13)
  - Cran-Craw 1971-1978 (Box 3 of 13)
  - Cre 1985-1988 (Box 3 of 13)
  - Cri-Cru, 1975-1984 (Box 3 of 13)
  - Cus-Cy, 1978 (Box 3 of 13)
  - Cu-Cur, 1977-1987 (Box 3 of 13)
  - Coan, E.V. (Box 3 of 13)
  - D, 2002 (Box 3 of 13)
  - D, 1998 (Box 3 of 13)
  - D, 1997 (Box 3 of 13)
  - D, 1996 (Box 3 of 13)
  - D. 1994 (Box 3 of 13)
  - D, 1993 (Box 3 of 13)
  - D, 1995 (Box 3 of 13)
  - D, 1990 (Box 3 of 13)
  - D, 1992 (Box 3 of 13)
  - D, 1991 (Box 3 of 13)
  - D, 1989 (Box 3 of 13)
  - Da-Dal, 1977-1983 (Box 3 of 13)
  - Dam-Dan, 1975-1985 (Box 3 of 13)
  - Dao-Dar, 1978-1982 (Box 3 of 13)
  - Das-Dau, 1977-1988 (Box 3 of 13)
  - Dav, 1978-1987 (Box 3 of 13)
  - Davis, George M. (Box 3 of 13)
  - Daw, 1977-1990 (Box 3 of 13)
  - Day-Daz, 1977-1990 (Box 3 of 13)
  - Dea-Dec, 1975-1984 (Box 3 of 13)
  - Ded-Dek, 1984-1985 (Box 3 of 13)
  - Del, 1976-1986 (Box 3 of 13)
  - Dem-Den, 1975-1988 (Box 3 of 13)
  - Deo-Dot, 1981 (Box 3 of 13)
  - Deu-Dez, 1976-1984 (Box 3 of 13)
  - Dhamankar, Mr. V. K. (Box 3 of 13)
  - Dia-Dic, 1980 (Box 3 of 13)
  - Did-Dig, 1982-1987 (Box 3 of 13)
  - Dih-Dip, 1975-1983 (Box 3 of 13)
  - Dir-Diz, 1977-1983 (Box 3 of 13)
  - Doa-Dok, 1983-1988 (Box 3 of 13)
  - Dol-Dom, 1980 (Box 3 of 13)
  - Don, 1975-1983 (Box 3 of 13)
  - Dance, S. P. (Box 3 of 13)
  - Demond, Joan (Box 3 of 13)
  - Dexter, Ralph W. (Box 3 of 13)
  - Drake, Robert J., 1944 (Box 3 of 13)
  - Doo-Dot, 1976 (Box 3 of 13)
  - Dou-Doz, 1975-1985 (Box 3 of 13)
  - Dra, 1976-1979 (Box 3 of 13)
  - Dre, 1980 (Box 3 of 13)
  - Dri, 1985 (Box 3 of 13)
  - Duc-Duk, 1975-1985 (Box 3 of 13)
  - Dul-Dum, 1084 (Box 3 of 13)
  - Dun, 1978-1988 (Box 3 of 13)
  - Duo-Dur, 1975-1978 (Box 3 of 13)
  - Dus-Dz, 1975-1987 (Box 3 of 13)
- Box 4
  - E, 1997 (Box 4 of 13)
  - E, 1996 (Box 4 of 13)
  - E, 1995 (Box 4 of 13)
  - E, 1994 (Box 4 of 13)
  - E,1993 (Box 4 of 13)
  - E, 1992 (Box 4 of 13)
  - E, 1991 (Box 4 of 13)
  - E, 1990 (Box 4 of 13)
  - E, 1989 (Box 4 of 13)
  - Ea-Eal, 1983-1986 (Box 4 of 13)
  - Eam-Ear, 1978-1985 (Box 4 of 13)
  - Eas-Eaz, 1977 (Box 4 of 13)
  - Eb-Ec, 1977-1985 (Box 4 of 13)
  - Ed, 1976-1987 (Box 4 of 13)
  - Ef-Ek, 1975-1988 (Box 4 of 13)
  - El, 1978-1988 (Box 4 of 13)
  - Em, 1977-1980 (Box 4 of 13)
  - Emerson, W. K. (2 Folders) (Box 4 of 13)
  - Emerson, William K. (Box 4 of 13)
  - En, 1986 (Box 4 of 13)
  - Eo-Er, 1977-1986 (Box 4 of 13)
  - Es-Eu, 1977-1988 (Box 4 of 13)
  - Ev-Er, 1976-1987 (Box 4 of 13)
  - Eldridge (Box 4 of 13)
  - F, 2003 (Box 4 of 13)
  - F, 2001 (Box 4 of 13)
  - F, 2000 (Box 4 of 13)
  - F, 1998 (Box 4 of 13)
  - F, 1995 (Box 4 of 13)
  - F, 1994 (Box 4 of 13)
  - F, 1993 (Box 4 of 13)
  - F, 1996 (Box 4 of 13)
  - F, 1991 (Box 4 of 13)
  - F, 1990 (Box 4 of 13)
  - F, 1992 (Box 4 of 13)
  - F, 1989 (Box 4 of 13)
  - Faa-Faq, 1975-1988 (Box 4 of 13)
  - Far, 1979 (Box 4 of 13)
  - Fas-Faz, 1975-1986 (Box 4 of 13)
  - Fea-Fel, 1976-1986 (Box 4 of 13)
  - Fem-Feq, 1977-1987 (Box 4 of 13)
  - Fer, 1979-1985 (Box 4 of 13)
  - Fia-Fil, 1980-1988 (Box 4 of 13)
  - Fim-Fir, 1979-1987 (Box 4 of 13)
  - Fischer-Fisher (Box 4 of 13)
  - Fla-Fli, 1980-1985 (Box 4 of 13)
  - Flo-Fly, 1985-1988 (Box 4 of 13)
  - Foa-Fon, 1976-1988 (Box 4 of 13)
  - For, 1976-1981 (Box 4 of 13)
  - Fos-Fou, 1975-1985 (Box 4 of 13)
  - Fow-Foz, 1975 (Box 4 of 13)
  - Fra, 1975-1985 (Box 4 of 13)
  - Fre, 1970-1986 (Box 4 of 13)
  - Fre, 1986 (Box 4 of 13)
  - Fu-Fy, 1978-1987 (Box 4 of 13)
  - Fischer-Piette, E (Box 4 of 13)
  - G, 2003 (Box 4 of 13)
  - G, 2002 (Box 4 of 13)
  - G, 2001 (Box 4 of 13)
  - G, 2000 (Box 4 of 13)
  - G, 1998 (Box 4 of 13)
  - G, 1997 (Box 4 of 13)
  - G, 1996 (Box 4 of 13)
  - G, 1995 (Box 4 of 13)
  - G, 1994 (Box 4 of 13)
  - G, 1993 (Box 4 of 13)
  - G, 1991 (Box 4 of 13)
  - G, 1990 (Box 4 of 13)
  - G, 1989 (Box 4 of 13)
  - G, 1992 (Box 4 of 13)
  - Gaa-Gak, 1978-1996 (Box 4 of 13)
  - Gal, 1979-1986 (Box 4 of 13)
  - Gam-Gaq, 1994 (Box 4 of 13)
  - Gar, 1975-1987 (Box 4 of 13)
  - Gas-Gaz, 1975-1980 (Box 4 of 13)
  - Gea-Geq, 1984-1988 (Box 4 of 13)
  - Ger-Gez, 1975-1988 (Box 4 of 13)
  - Gh, 1978 (Box 4 of 13)
  - Gia-Gik, 1982-1986 (Box 4 of 13)
  - Gil, 1982-1988 (Box 4 of 13)
  - Gin-Giz, 1976-1988 (Box 4 of 13)
  - Gl, 1980-1992 (Box 4 of 13)
  - Gm-Gol, 1975-1986 (Box 4 of 13)
  - Gom-Gon, 1975-1987 (Box 4 of 13)
  - Gop-Gor, 1975-1986 (Box 4 of 13)
  - Gos-Goz, 1977-1987 (Box 4 of 13)
  - Gar, 1977-1982 (Box 4 of 13)
- Box 5
  - Gre, 1975-1987 (Box 5 of 13)
  - Gri, 1975-1983 (Box 5 of 13)
  - Gro-Gru, 1975-1986 (Box 5 of 13)
  - Gua-Guk, 1975-1988 (Box 5 of 13)
  - Gul-Gur, 1979-1985 (Box 5 of 13)
  - Gus-Guz, 1981-1986 (Box 5 of 13)
  - H, 2003 (Box 5 of 13)
  - H, 2002 (Box 5 of 13)
  - H, 2000 (Box 5 of 13)
  - H, 2001 (Box 5 of 13)
  - H, 1999 (Box 5 of 13)
  - H, 1995 (Box 5 of 13)
  - H, 1992 (Box 5 of 13)
  - H, 1992 (Box 5 of 13)
  - H, 1991 (Box 5 of 13)
  - H, 1998 (Box 5 of 13)
  - H, 1994 (Box 5 of 13)
  - H, 1996 (Box 5 of 13)
  - H, 1990 (Box 5 of 13)
  - H, 1989 (Box 5 of 13)
  - Haa-Hak, 1976-1985 (Box 5 of 13)
  - Hal, 1975-1984 (Box 5 of 13)
  - Han, 1977-1994 (Box 5 of 13)
  - Harr, 1978-1980 (Box 5 of 13)
  - Hao-Harq, 1977-1994 (Box 5 of 13)
  - Habe, Tadashige (Box 5 of 13)
  - Helper, N. M. (Box 5 of 13)
  - Bercaw-Hochberg, Natasha (Box 5 of 13)
  - Hobricht, Leslie (Box 5 of 13)
  - Hart-Hav, 1980-1988 (Box 5 of 13)
  - Haw-Haz, 1978-1982 (Box 5 of 13)
  - Hea-Hem, 1977-1991 (Box 5 of 13)
  - Hen-Heq, 1985-1988 (Box 5 of 13)
  - Her, 1979-1987 (Box 5 of 13)
  - Hes-Hez, 1976-1988 (Box 5 of 13)
  - Hia-Hik, 1975-1988 (Box 5 of 13)
  - Him-Hiq, 1986 (Box 5 of 13)
  - Hir-His, 1979 (Box 5 of 13)
  - Hit-Hiz, 1981 (Box 5 of 13)
  - Hoa-Hoe, 1977-1988 (Box 5 of 13)
  - Hof, 1976-1988 (Box 5 of 13)
  - Hol, 1978-1988 (Box 5 of 13)
  - Hog-Hok, 1983 (Box 5 of 13)
  - Hom-Hoq, 1978-1980 (Box 5 of 13)
  - Har-Hav, 1984-1989 (Box 5 of 13)
  - How, 1977-1980 (2 folders) (Box 5 of 13)
  - Hox-Hoz, 1979 (Box 5 of 13)
  - Hua-Huf, 1978-1987 (Box 5 of 13)
  - Hug-Hum, 1983-1986 (Box 5 of 13)
  - Hun-Huq, 1975 (Box 5 of 13)
  - Hur-Hut, 1964-1989 (Box 5 of 13)
  - Huu-Huz, 1977 (Box 5 of 13)
  - Harasewych (2 Folders) (Box 5 of 13)
- Box 6
  - Houbrick (2 folders) (Box 6 of 13)
  - Paramelanians (Box 6 of 13)
  - Fiji Shells (Box 6 of 13)
  - Cor. Prec. Ship. (Box 6 of 13)
  - 1991 Transactions (Box 6 of 13)
  - Houbrick's transactions (Box 6 of 13)
  - Houbrick's return of loans (Box 6 of 13)
  - I, 1998 (Box 6 of 13)
  - I, 1996 (Box 6 of 13)
  - I, 1995 (Box 6 of 13)
  - I, 1994 (Box 6 of 13)
  - I, 1992 (Box 6 of 13)
  - I, 1991 (Box 6 of 13)
  - I, 1990 (Box 6 of 13)
  - I, 1989 (Box 6 of 13)
  - Ia-Im, 1988 (Box 6 of 13)
  - In, 1978-1987 (Box 6 of 13)
  - Ir-It, 1988 (Box 6 of 13)
  - Iu-Iz, 1979-1989 (Box 6 of 13)
  - J, 2003 (Box 6 of 13)
  - J, 2001 (Box 6 of 13)
  - J, 1998 (Box 6 of 13)
  - J, 1997 (Box 6 of 13)
  - J, 1996 (Box 6 of 13)
  - J, 1995 (Box 6 of 13)
  - J, 1993 (Box 6 of 13)
  - J, 1994 (Box 6 of 13)
  - J, 1992 (Box 6 of 13)
  - J, 1991 (Box 6 of 13)
  - J, 1990 (Box 6 of 13)
  - J, 1989 (Box 6 of 13)
  - Ja-Jack, 1982 (Box 6 of 13)
  - Jack-Jacz, 1980 (Box 6 of 13)
  - Jad-Jal, 1975-1983 (Box 6 of 13)
  - Jam-Jao, 1976-1985 (Box 6 of 13)
  - Jar-Jaz, 1977-1985 (Box 6 of 13)
  - Jea-Jek, 1985 (Box 6 of 13)
  - Jel-Jen, 1975-1984 (Box 6 of 13)
  - Jeo-Jez, 1977 (Box 6 of 13)
  - Johnson (2 folders) (Box 6 of 13)
  - Jom-Jon, 1983-1984 (Box 6 of 13)
  - Joo-Joz, 1975-1985 (Box 6 of 13)
  - Jua-Jum, 1983 (Box 6 of 13)
  - Jackson, Robert T. (Box 6 of 13)
  - Jacobson, M. K. (Box 6 of 13)
  - Jaume, Miguel L. (Box 6 of 13)
  - Johnson, Richard I. (Box 6 of 13)
  - K, 2001 (Box 6 of 13)
  - K, 1997 (Box 6 of 13)
  - K, 1996 (Box 6 of 13)
  - K, 1993 (Box 6 of 13)
  - K,1994 (Box 6 of 13)
  - K, 1995 (Box 6 of 13)
  - K, 1992 (Box 6 of 13)
  - K, 1991 (Box 6 of 13)
  - K, 1990 (Box 6 of 13)
  - K, 1989 (Box 6 of 13)
  - Ka, 1975-1989 (Box 6 of 13)
  - Ke-Kek, 1978-1983 (Box 6 of 13)
  - Kel-Kem, 1976-1985 (Box 6 of 13)
  - Ken-Kez, 1978-1985 (Box 6 of 13)
  - Kia-Kim, 1975-1985 (Box 6 of 13)
  - Kin, 1975-1985 (Box 6 of 13)
  - Kir-Kiz ,1979-1984 (Box 6 of 13)
  - Kl, 1976-1986 (Box 6 of 13)
  - Kin, 1971-1988 (Box 6 of 13)
  - Koa-Kok, 1977-1987 (Box 6 of 13)
  - Kol-Koz, 1975-1981 (Box 6 of 13)
  - Kr, 1977-1983 (Box 6 of 13)
- Box 7
  - Ku, 1975-1991 (Box 7 of 13)
  - Kaicher, Mrs. J. J. (Box 7 of 13)
  - Kay, Dr. Alison (Box 7 of 13)
  - Keen, A. Myra (Box 7 of 13)
  - Kilburn (Box 7 of 13)
  - Knudson, Dr. Jorgen (Box 7 of 13)
  - Kohn, Alan J. (Box 7 of 13)
  - Kondo, Yoshio (Box 7 of 13)
  - L, 2001 (Box 7 of 13)
  - L, 1998 (Box 7 of 13)
  - L, 1996 (Box 7 of 13)
  - L, 1994 (Box 7 of 13)
  - L, 1993 (Box 7 of 13)
  - L, 1995 (Box 7 of 13)
  - L, 1007 (Box 7 of 13)
  - L,1992 (Box 7 of 13)
  - L, 1991 (Box 7 of 13)
  - L, 1990 (Box 7 of 13)
  - L, 1989 (Box 7 of 13)
  - La-Lal, 1986 (Box 7 of 13)
  - Lam, 1975-1979 (Box 7 of 13)
  - Lan, 1977-1985 (Box 7 of 13)
  - Lao-Lar, 1977-1981 (Box 7 of 13)
  - Las-Law, 1976-1984 (Box 7 of 13)
  - Law-Laz, 1988 (Box 7 of 13)
  - Lea-Lec, 1979-1988 (Box 7 of 13)
  - Led-Leh, 1976-1986 (Box 7 of 13)
  - Lei-Len, 1978 (Box 7 of 13)
  - Leo-Lev, 1976-1982 (Box 7 of 13)
  - Lew-Lez, 1975-1988 (Box 7 of 13)
  - Lia-Lim, 1980-1990 (Box 7 of 13)
  - Lin-Linder, 1976-1987 (Box 7 of 13)
  - Linds-Linz, 1979-1988 (Box 7 of 13)
  - Lio-Liz, 1976-1979 (Box 7 of 13)
  - Loa-Lon, 1979-1981 (Box 7 of 13)
  - Loo- Loz, 1975-1992 (Box 7 of 13)
  - Lua-Luk, 1975-1982 (Box 7 of 13)
  - Lul-Luz, 1981-1983 (Box 7 of 13)
  - Ly, 1982-1984 (Box 7 of 13)
  - Ladd, Harry S. (Box 7 of 13)
  - Lyman, F. (Box 7 of 13)
  - Lyons, W. G. (Box 7 of 13)
  - M, 2005 (Box 7 of 13)
  - M, 2003 (Box 7 of 13)
  - M, 2002 (Box 7 of 13)
  - M, 2001 (Box 7 of 13)
  - M, 2000 (Box 7 of 13)
  - M, 1999 (Box 7 of 13)
  - M, 1996 (Box 7 of 13)
  - M, 1998 (Box 7 of 13)
  - M, 1997 (Box 7 of 13)
  - M, 1995 (Box 7 of 13)
  - M, 1994 (Box 7 of 13)
  - M, 1992 (Box 7 of 13)
  - M, 1989 (Box 7 of 13)
  - M, 1993 (Box 7 of 13)
  - MC, 1993 (Box 7 of 13)
  - MC, 1992 (Box 7 of 13)
  - MC, 1990 (Box 7 of 13)
  - M, 1990 (Box 7 of 13)
  - M, 1991 (Box 7 of 13)
  - MC, 1991 (Box 7 of 13)
  - Maa- Mac, 1975-1985 (Box 7 of 13)
  - MacA-MacM, 1980- 1989 (Box 7 of 13)
  - MacN-Macz, 1975-1980 (Box 7 of 13)
  - Mad-Mak, 1980 1988 (Box 7 of 13)
  - Mangold, Katherine (Box 7 of 13)
- Box 8
  - Mal-Map, 1975-1985 (Box 8 of 13)
  - Mar-Marr, 1975-1988 (Box 8 of 13)
  - Mrs, 1978-1988 (Box 8 of 13)
  - Mart, 1983-1988 (Box 8 of 13)
  - Maru-Marz, 1983 (Box 8 of 13)
  - Mau-Maz, 1983 (Box 8 of 13)
  - Mas-Mat, 1978-1981 (Box 8 of 13)
  - Mc, 1989 (Box 8 of 13)
  - McA-McC, 1976 (Box 8 of 13)
  - McD-McG, 1976-1984 (Box 8 of 13)
  - McH-McK, 1983-1987 (Box 8 of 13)
  - McL, 1976-1988 (Box 8 of 13)
  - McM-McZ, 1977-1980 (Box 8 of 13)
  - Mea-Mek, 1983-1991 (Box 8 of 13)
  - Mel-Mep, 1976-1983 (Box 8 of 13)
  - Mer, 1975-1978 (Box 8 of 13)
  - Merrill (Box 8 of 13)
  - Mes-Mez, 1976-1988 (Box 8 of 13)
  - Milm-Mis, 1980-1987 (Box 8 of 13)
  - Milm-Mis, 1986 (Box 8 of 13)
  - Mit-Miz, 1984 (Box 8 of 13)
  - Moa-Mol, 1975-1987 (2 folders) (Box 8 of 13)
  - Mom-Moo, 1908-1984 (Box 8 of 13)
  - Moore (Box 8 of 13)
  - Mop-Mor, 1976-1988 (Box 8 of 13)
  - Mors-Morz, 1975-1988 (Box 8 of 13)
  - Morris (Box 8 of 13)
  - Mos-Moz, 1975-1986 (Box 8 of 13)
  - Mu-Mum, 1977-1980 (Box 8 of 13)
  - Mun-Mup, 1975-1994 (Box 8 of 13)
  - Mur, 1975-1984 (Box 8 of 13)
  - Mus-My, 1975-1983 (Box 8 of 13)
  - Marcus, E. (Box 8 of 13)
  - Miller, Bruce A. (Box 8 of 13)
  - Moore, D. R. (Box 8 of 13)
  - Morison, J. P. E. (Box 8 of 13)
  - N, 1998 (Box 8 of 13)
  - N, 1996 (Box 8 of 13)
  - N, 1995 (Box 8 of 13)
  - N, 1994 (Box 8 of 13)
  - N, 1993 (Box 8 of 13)
  - N, 1992 (Box 8 of 13)
  - N, 1991 (Box 8 of 13)
  - N, 1990 (Box 8 of 13)
  - N, 1989 (Box 8 of 13)
  - National Capital Shell Club (Box 8 of 13)
  - Na-Naq, 1975-1987 (Box 8 of 13)
  - Nar-Naz, 1975-1986 (Box 8 of 13)
  - Ne-Nek, 1981-1986 (Box 8 of 13)
  - Nel-Nez, 1976-1986 (Box 8 of 13)
  - Nia-Nif, 1985-1986 (Box 8 of 13)
  - Nig-Niz, 1975-1986 (Box 8 of 13)
  - Noa-Noq, 1979-1983 (Box 8 of 13)
  - Nor, 1975-1985 (Box 8 of 13)
  - Nos-Noz, 1979-1983 (Box 8 of 13)
  - Nu-Nz, 1978-1988 (Box 8 of 13)
  - Newman, W. A. (Box 8 of 13)
  - Nicol, David (Box 8 of 13)
  - O, 1997 (Box 8 of 13)
  - O, 1996 (Box 8 of 13)
  - O, 1991 (Box 8 of 13)
  - O, 1993 (Box 8 of 13)
  - O, 1994 (Box 8 of 13)
  - O, 1995 (Box 8 of 13)
  - O, 1995 (Box 8 of 13)
  - O, 1989 (Box 8 of 13)
- Box 9
  - Oa-Oc, 1975-1985 (Box 9 of 13)
  - Od-Ok, 1975-1988 (Box 9 of 13)
  - Ol, 1979-1994 (Box 9 of 13)
  - Om-Oq, 1976-1983 (Box 9 of 13)
  - Or, 1986-1993 (Box 9 of 13)
  - Os, 1964-1984 (Box 9 of 13)
  - Ou-Oz, 1981-1994 (Box 9 of 13)
  - Oehser, P. H. (Box 9 of 13)
  - Ols, William F. (Box 9 of 13)
  - Olsson, A. A. (Box 9 of 13)
  - P, 2001 (Box 9 of 13)
  - P, 2000 (Box 9 of 13)
  - P, 1998 (Box 9 of 13)
  - P, 1997 (Box 9 of 13)
  - P, 1994 (Box 9 of 13)
  - P, 1996 (Box 9 of 13)
  - P, 1995 (Box 9 of 13)
  - P, 1993 (Box 9 of 13)
  - P, 1992 (Box 9 of 13)
  - P, 1991 (Box 9 of 13)
  - P, 1990 (Box 9 of 13)
  - P, 1989 (Box 9 of 13)
  - Pa-Paf, 1977-1986 (Box 9 of 13)
  - Pag-Pak, 1975-1983 (Box 9 of 13)
  - Pal, 1978-1986 (Box 9 of 13)
  - Pam-Paq, 1979 (Box 9 of 13)
  - Park, 1982-1988 (Box 9 of 13)
  - Parl-Parz, 1975-1978 (Box 9 of 13)
  - Paz-Paz, 1975-1980 (Box 9 of 13)
  - Pea-Pem, 1975-1987 (Box 9 of 13)
  - Pen-Peq, 1984-1987 (Box 9 of 13)
  - Per, 1983-1988 (Box 9 of 13)
  - Pes-Pet, 1966-1985 (Box 9 of 13)
  - Peu-Pez, 1981 (Box 9 of 13)
  - Pf, 1978 (Box 9 of 13)
  - Ph, 1984-1988 (Box 9 of 13)
  - Pl, 1984-1988 (Box 9 of 13)
  - Po-Pom, 1980-1988 (Box 9 of 13)
  - Pi-Pik, 1975-1986 (Box 9 of 13)
  - Pil-Piz, 1979-1986 (Box 9 of 13)
  - Pon-Por, 1976-1988 (Box 9 of 13)
  - Pos-Pov, 1976-1984 (Box 9 of 13)
  - Pow-Poz, 1979-1986 (Box 9 of 13)
  - Pra, 1976-1983 (Box 9 of 13)
  - Pre-Pric, 1980-1987 (Box 9 of 13)
  - Prid-Priz, 1977-1987 (Box 9 of 13)
  - Pro-Pry, 1976-1987 (Box 9 of 13)
  - Pu-Py, 1977-1988 (Box 9 of 13)
  - Parodiz, Juan J. (Box 9 of 13)
  - Paulay, G. (Box 9 of 13)
  - Petit, Richard E. (Box 9 of 13)
  - Ponder, Winston F. (2 folders) (Box 9 of 13)
  - Powell, Awb (Box 9 of 13)
  - Prezant (Box 9 of 13)
  - Q, 2001 (Box 9 of 13)
  - Q, 1998 (Box 9 of 13)
  - Q, 1997 (Box 9 of 13)
  - Q, 1996 (Box 9 of 13)
  - Q, 1994 (Box 9 of 13)
  - Q, 1993 (Box 9 of 13)
  - Q, 1992 (Box 9 of 13)
  - Q, 1991 (Box 9 of 13)
  - Q, 1990 (Box 9 of 13)
  - Q, 1989 (Box 9 of 13)
  - Qua-Que, 1977-1983 (Box 9 of 13)
  - Qui, 1975-1988 (Box 9 of 13)
  - R, 2002 (Box 9 of 13)
  - R, 2001 (Box 9 of 13)
  - R, 1995 (Box 9 of 13)
  - R, 1994 (Box 9 of 13)
  - R, 2000 (Box 9 of 13)
  - R, 1997 (Box 9 of 13)
  - R, 1996 (Box 9 of 13)
  - R, 1993 (Box 9 of 13)
  - R, 1992 (Box 9 of 13)
  - R, 1991 (Box 9 of 13)
  - R, 1990 (Box 9 of 13)
  - R, 1989 (Box 9 of 13)
- Box 10
  - Ra-Rah, 1976-1982 (Box 10 of 13)
  - Rai-Ram, 1980-1987 (Box 10 of 13)
  - Ran, 1975-1985 (Box 10 of 13)
  - Rao-Rat, 1979-1987 (Box 10 of 13)
  - Rau-Raz, 1976-1984 (Box 10 of 13)
  - Rea-Reh, 1975-1988 (Box 10 of 13)
  - Rei, 1979-1983 (Box 10 of 13)
  - Rej-Rev, 1977-1990 (Box 10 of 13)
  - Rew-Rez, 1978-1985 (Box 10 of 13)
  - Rh, 1981 (Box 10 of 13)
  - Ri-Rice, 1978-1988 (Box 10 of 13)
  - Rich-Ricz, 1979 (Box 10 of 13)
  - Richards-Richardson, 1975-1985 (Box 10 of 13)
  - Rid-Rik, 1977-1985 (Box 10 of 13)
  - Rio-Rit, 1975-1985 (Box 10 of 13)
  - Riu-Riz, 1975 (Box 10 of 13)
  - Roa-Robe, 1977-1984 (Box 10 of 13)
  - Robi-Robz, 1980-1988 (Box 10 of 13)
  - Roc-Rof, 1977-1990 (Box 10 of 13)
  - Radwin, George E. (Box 10 of 13)
  - Randall, John E. (Box 10 of 13)
  - Rehder, Herald A. (Box 10 of 13)
  - Robertson, R. (Box 10 of 13)
  - Rog-Roo, 1981-1984 (Box 10 of 13)
  - Rop-Ros, 1958-1982 (Box 10 of 13)
  - Rot-Roz, 1975-1995 (Box 10 of 13)
  - Ru, 1977-1983 (Box 10 of 13)
  - Ry, 1980 (Box 10 of 13)
  - Roper, C. F. E. (2 folders) (Box 10 of 13)
  - Rosewater mem. (?) SVC (?) (Box 10 of 13)
  - Rosewater, J. (2 folders) (Box 10 of 13)
  - S, 1993 (Box 10 of 13)
  - S, 1996 (Box 10 of 13)
  - S, 2001 (Box 10 of 13)
  - S, 2000 (Box 10 of 13)
  - S, 1999 (Box 10 of 13)
  - S, 1998 (Box 10 of 13)
  - S, 1994 (Box 10 of 13)
  - S, 1993 (Box 10 of 13)
  - S, 1997 (Box 10 of 13)
  - S, 1995 (Box 10 of 13)
  - S, 1992 (Box 10 of 13)
  - S, 1991 (Box 10 of 13)
  - S, 1990 (Box 10 of 13)
  - S, 1989 (Box 10 of 13)
- Box 11
  - S, 2003 (Box 11 of 13)
  - S, 2002 (Box 11 of 13)
  - S, 2004 (Box 11 of 13)
  - Sanchez (Box 11 of 13)
  - Sa-Sal, 1984-1986 (Box 11 of 13)
  - Sam-San, 1971-1986 (Box 11 of 13)
  - Sao-Sau, 1976-1983 (Box 11 of 13)
  - Sav-Saz, 1975-1985 (Box 11 of 13)
  - Sca-Sche, 1975-1978 (Box 11 of 13)
  - Schi-Schn, 1977-1988 (Box 11 of 13)
  - Scho-Schr, 1975 (Box 11 of 13)
  - Schu-Schw, 1976-1986 (Box 11 of 13)
  - Sci-Scu, 1983-1988 (Box 11 of 13)
  - Si-Sy, 1970-1990 (3 Folders) (Box 11 of 13)
  - Sea-Sez, 1970-1982 (Box 11 of 13)
  - Sha-Shu, 1975-1985 (Box 11 of 13)
  - Salvat, Bernard, 1975-1985 (Box 11 of 13)